<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thanks for installing AnkiDroid!<br />This is a short introduction.<br />What you see now is the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>question</span> part of a flashcard.<br />Please click on the large button below...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The next card is shown now.<br />The idea is straightforward: Just like in &quot;real world&quot; paper flashcards, you write a question on the front and the answer on the back side of your cards.<br />(click the button to show the back side)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Ovanför varje svarsknapp hittar du information om tiden till nästa gång detta kort kommer att visas om den knappen används för att svara kortet.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Tanken är att visa dig kortet igen precis innan du gömmer bort det. Empiriska studier har visat att information kan läras in mest effektivt på det här sättet.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Lite kort om strukturen i AnkiDroid:<br /><br>All information måste anges som svar och fråga. Om du vill lära dig båda vägarna bör du skapa ett nytt kort som byter plats på svaret och frågan.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Kort läggs samman i kortlekar och kan organiseras med hjälp av taggar.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[There are mainly two ways of getting new cards:<br />You either add premade decks of other users (choose &quot;shared decks&quot; in the decks summary) or create them by yourself.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Men att skapa egna kortlekar är troligen bäst för dina egna behov. Du kan göra detta direkt i AnkiDroid...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s have a look on the top bar:<br />In the left top corner you find some numbers. The blue one tells you, how many new cards are still projected for today. The red number counts the failed cards (answered by &quot;again&quot;),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[I det högra hörnet hittar du information om använd tid för detta kort och om dina framsteg.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Albeit you can use AnkiDroid stand alone, it is fully connected to AnkiWeb, the syncing server of Anki Desktop (available for Linux, Windows, Mac).]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Detta har varit de viktigaste punkterna vid användning av AnkiDroid.<br /><br>För mer information om funktioner och användningsområden, gå till http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[... in order to see the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>answer</span> part of the flashcard (below the line).<br />Click on the button on the right]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s assume you want to learn the world\'s capitals. Let the question be...<br />(click on one of the buttons to show the next card)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Denna tid beräknas utifrån när du senast svarade på kortet, knappen du använder för att svara på kortet nu och tidigare svar av kortet.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Om du vill lära dig mer om intervallbaserad repetition, besök:<br>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Detta kan göras automatiskt. Du behöver inte ange samma information två gånger.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Du kommer att lära dig detta snabbt när du börjar använda AnkiDroid.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You\'ll find thousands of premade decks to download and there are probably some which are useful for you.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[... eller (något enklare) med hjälp av skrivbordsmjukvaran Anki (som kan laddas ner gratis här http://ankisrs.net/).<br><br>Du kan synkronisera dina kortlekar mellan AnkiDroid och Anki väldigt enkelt, så det är inga problem att föra över dem.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[the green one shows the number of cards you\'ve already learned before and which are due to review today.<br />The type of the actual cards is specified by an underline.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Den övre stapeln visar dina framsteg och den undre visar andelen korrekta svar.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thus, you can easily sync your collection between AnkiDroid and Anki Desktop and use the latter for a more convenient card adding and managing.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Prova att använda det nu en stund och se om det passar just dig.<br><br>Börja med kortlekssammanfattningen (tryck meny på huvudskärmen och välj &quot;alla kortlekar&quot;). Där kan du ladda ner färdiga kortlekar eller skapa dina egna (använd menyn där).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>