<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thanks for installing AnkiDroid!<br />This is a short introduction.<br />What you see now is the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>question</span> part of a flashcard.<br />Please click on the large button below...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The next card is shown now.<br />The idea is straightforward: Just like in &quot;real world&quot; paper flashcards, you write a question on the front and the answer on the back side of your cards.<br />(click the button to show the back side)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Acima de todos os botões de resposta, você encontra informações sobre o tempo, após o qual o cartão será mostrado novamente quando respondido por este botão.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[A intenção é mostrar-lhe novamente o cartão imediatamente antes que você o esqueceria. Estudos empíricos demonstraram que por esta via informações podem ser aprendidas com a maior eficiência.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Algumas palavras sobre a organização em AnkiDroid:<br/><br>Todas as informações tem de ser colocada em pares de pergunta e resposta. Se você quer aprender em outra direção, você deveria criar outro cartão com as informações trocadas.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Cartões são postos junto em decks e lá podem ser organizados com a ajuda de todos os tipos de tags.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[There are mainly two ways of getting new cards:<br />You either add premade decks of other users (choose &quot;shared decks&quot; in the decks summary) or create them by yourself.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[De qualquer forma, criar seus próprios decks é essencial para atender perfeitamente às suas necessidades. Você pode fazer isso diretamente no AnkiDroid...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s have a look on the top bar:<br />In the left top corner you find some numbers. The red one counts the failed cards (answered by &quot;again&quot;),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[No canto direito, você encontra informações sobre seu tempo de pensando neste cartão e sobre seu desempenho.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Albeit you can use AnkiDroid stand alone, it is fully connected to AnkiWeb, the syncing server of Anki Desktop (available for Linux, Windows, Mac).]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Estes têm sido os principais pontos de uso do AnkiDroid.<br/><br>Para obter mais informações sobre o conceito chave do Anki, visite http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[... in order to see the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>answer</span> part of the flashcard (below the line).<br />Click on the button on the right]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s assume you want to learn the world\'s capitals. Let the question be...<br />(click on one of the buttons to show the next card)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Este período de tempo é calculado sobre a última vez que você respondeu o cartão, a escolha atual de dificuldade e opções de dificuldade de respostas anteriores deste cartão.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Se você quiser saber mais sobre repetições espaçadas, visite:<br>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Não se preocupe, isso pode ser feito automaticamente. Não há necessidade de inserir a mesma informação duas vezes.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Você vai aprender isso rapidamente quando você começar a usar o AnkiDroid.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You\'ll find thousands of premade decks to download and there are probably some which are useful for you.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[...ou(um pouco mais conveniente) com o aplicativo de desktop Anki(disponível gratuitamente em http://ankisrs.net/).<br><br>Você pode sincronizar seus decks com o aplicativo de desktop facilmente, então transferir os dados não é um problema.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[the black one shows the number of cards you\'ve already learned before and which are due to review today, and the blue number tells you, how many new cards are projected for today. <br />The type of the actual cards is specified by an underline.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[A barra superior mostra seu progresso, a inferior indica o percentual de respostas Sim.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thus, you can easily sync your collection between AnkiDroid and Anki Desktop and use the latter for a more convenient card adding and managing.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Experimente-o um pouco agora e veja se ele se encaixa às suas necessidades.<br><br>Que tal começar com a visão geral de decks(aperte menu na tela principal e escolha &quot;todos os pavimentos&quot;)onde você pode baixar decks prontos ou criar seu próprio(basta usar o menu de lá).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>