<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thanks for installing AnkiDroid!<br />This is a short introduction.<br />What you see now is the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>question</span> part of a flashcard.<br />Please click on the large button below&#8]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The next card is shown now.<br />The idea is straightforward: Just like in &quot;real world&quot; paper flashcards, you write a question on the front and the answer on the back side of your cards.<br />(click the button to show the back side)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Nad každým tlačítkem pro ohodnocení odpovědi vidíte informaci o čase, za který se karta znovu zobrazí, pokud jej zvolíte.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Záměrem je zobrazit kartu znovu bezprostředně před tím, než by jste ji zapomněli. Empirické studie ukazují, že se lze takto učit mnohem efektivněji.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Pár slov o organizaci v AnkiDroid:<br/><br>Veškeré informace musí být uvedeny v páru otázka/odpověď. Pokud se chcete učit i v opačném směru, měli byste vytvořit další kartu s prohozenými informacemi.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Karty jsou shromažďovány do balíčků a můžou být organizovány pomocí nejrůznějších štítků.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[There are mainly two ways of getting new cards:<br />You either add premade decks of other users (choose &quot;shared decks&quot; in the decks summary) or create them by yourself.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Nicméně, vytváření vlastních balíčků je důležité, aby vyhovovaly dokonale vašim potřebám. To můžete udělat přímo v AnkiDroid&#8]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s have a look on the top bar:<br />In the left top corner you find some numbers. The red one counts the failed cards (answered by &quot;again&quot;),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[V pravém rohu najdete informaci o čase přemyšlení nad aktuální kartou a vaše výsledky.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Albeit you can use AnkiDroid stand alone, it is fully connected to AnkiWeb, the syncing server of Anki Desktop (available for Linux, Windows, Mac).]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[To byly hlavní body použití AnkiDroid.<br/><br>Pro další informace o konceptu Anki, navštivte http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[tor>&#8230; in order to see the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>answer</span> part of the flashcard (below the line).<br />Click on the button on the right]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s assume you want to learn the world\'s capitals. Let the question be&#8230;<br />(click on one of the buttons to show the next card)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Tento čas se počítá podle předcházejících odpovědi na této kartě a volbě současné snadnosti této karty.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Pokud se chcete dozvědět více o rozloženém opakování, navštivte:<br>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Nebojte se, to lze provést automaticky. Není třeba vkládat stejné informace dvakrát.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Naučíte se to rychle, když začnete používat AnkiDroid.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You\'ll find thousands of premade decks to download and there are probably some which are useful for you.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[tor>&#8230; nebo (a o něco pohodlněji) v aplikaci pro pc Anki (zdarma ke stažení v http://ankisrs.net/).<br><br> Lze velmi snadno synchronizovat balíčky s aplikací pro pc, takže přenos dat není problém.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[the black one shows the number of cards you\'ve already learned before and which are due to review today, and the blue number tells you, how many new cards are projected for today. <br />The type of the actual cards is specified by an underline.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Horní pruh ukazuje váš proces učení, dolní udává procento odpovědí Ano.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thus, you can easily sync your collection between AnkiDroid and Anki Desktop and use the latter for a more convenient card adding and managing.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Zkuste to teď chvíli používat program a zjistěte, zda odpovídá vašim potřebám.<br><br>Možná, že můžete začít s přehledem balíčků (klikněte na menu na hlavní obrazovce a vyberte \"Všechny balíčky\"), kde si můžete stáhnout již vytvořené balíčky nebo si vytvořit vlastní (stačí zde použít menu).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>