<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[感谢安装AnkiDroid！<br/>这是一段简单的介绍<br/>你现在看到的是卡片的<span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>问题部分</span><br />试着点击一下下面那个大按钮]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Above every answer buttons, you find information about the time, after which the card will be shown again when answered by this button.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The intention is to show you the card again, immediately before you would forget it. Empirical studies have shown that by this means information can be learned most efficiently.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Cards are put together in decks and can there be organised by help of all sorts of tags.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[But anyway, creating own decks is essential to suit your needs perfectly. You can do this directly in AnkiDroid...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[现在看一下顶栏<br/>你可以在左上角找到一些数字。蓝色的表示今天还有多少新的卡片要学习，红色的表示失败的卡片（点击了\"再次学习\"),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Albeit you can use AnkiDroid stand alone, it is fully connected to AnkiWeb, the syncing server of Anki Desktop (available for Linux, Windows, Mac).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[... 来查看卡片上那条线下的<span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>答案</span><br />点击右边的按钮]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[This time period is calculated of the last time you answered the card, the current ease choice and ease choices of previous answers of that card.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[If you want to learn more about spaced repetition, visit:<br>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You will learn about that quickly when you start to use AnkiDroid.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[... or (a bit more convenient) with the desktop application Anki (downloadable for free under http://ankisrs.net/).<br><br>You can sync your decks with the desktop application very easily, so transfering the data is not a problem.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[绿色的表示之前已学而今天要复习的卡片数。<br/>下划线标注的，就是当前的卡片类型。]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thus, you can easily sync your collection between AnkiDroid and Anki Desktop and use the latter for a more convenient card adding and managing.]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>