<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Täname, et installisite AnkiDroidi!<br />See on lühike kasutusjuhend<br />Praegu näed sa<span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>küsimuse</span> poolt kaardist.<br />Palun kliki alloleval suurel nupul...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Nüüd näidatakse järgmist kaarti.<br />Idee on lihtne: just nagu &quot;pärismaailma&quot; kaartidel kirjutatakse küsimus kaardi esiküljele ja vastus tahaküljele.<br />(vajuta nuppu, et näha kaardi tagakülge)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Above every answer buttons, you find information about the time, after which the card will be shown again when answered by this button.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Eesmärk on näidata teile kaarti uuesti, vahetult enne kui te unustate selle. Empiirilised uuringud on näidanud, et see tähendab, et niimoodi teavet saab õppida kõige tõhusamalt.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Some words about the organisation in AnkiDroid:<br /><br>All information has to be put into pairs of question and answer. If you want to learn in the other direction, you should create another card with swapped information.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Cards are put together in decks and can there be organised by help of all sorts of tags.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[There are mainly two ways of getting new cards:<br />You either add premade decks of other users (choose &quot;shared decks&quot; in the decks summary) or create them by yourself.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[But anyway, creating own decks is essential to suit your needs perfectly. You can do this directly in AnkiDroid...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s have a look on the top bar:<br />In the left top corner you find some numbers. The blue one tells you, how many new cards are still projected for today. The red number counts the failed cards (answered by &quot;again&quot;),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[On the right corner you find information about your thinking time of this card and about your performance.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Albeit you can use AnkiDroid stand alone, it is fully connected to AnkiWeb, the syncing server of Anki Desktop (available for Linux, Windows, Mac).]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[These have been the main points of AnkiDroid usage.<br /><br>For more information about the key concept of Anki, visit http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[... et näha <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>vastuse</span> poolt kaardist (joone all).<br />Vajuta paremal asuvat nuppu]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Oletame, et sa tahad õppida maailma pealinnu. Olgu küsimus...<br />(vajuta üht nuppu, et näha järgmist kaarti)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[This time period is calculated of the last time you answered the card, the current ease choice and ease choices of previous answers of that card.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Kui soovite rohkem teada saada vahedega kordamine, külasta: <br>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Don\'t worry, this can be done automatically. There is no need of inserting the same information twice.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You will learn about that quickly when you start to use AnkiDroid.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You\'ll find thousands of premade decks to download and there are probably some which are useful for you.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[... or (a bit more convenient) with the desktop application Anki (downloadable for free under http://ankisrs.net/).<br><br>You can sync your decks with the desktop application very easily, so transfering the data is not a problem.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[the green one shows the number of cards you\'ve already learned before and which are due to review today.<br />The type of the actual cards is specified by an underline.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The upper bar shows your progress, the lower one indicates the percentage of yes answers.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thus, you can easily sync your collection between AnkiDroid and Anki Desktop and use the latter for a more convenient card adding and managing.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Just try it a bit out now and see, if it fits your needs.<br><br>Maybe start with the deck overview (hit menu on the main screen and choose &quot;all decks&quot;), where you can download premade decks or create your own (just use the menu there).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>