<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Andrew <andrewdubya@gmail> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Edu Zamora <edu.zasu@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Daniel Svaerd <daniel.svard@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Nicolas Raoul <nicolas.raoul@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2010 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
<!--Generated by crowdin.net-->
<resources>
  <string name="welcome_message">Com AnkiDroid Voce pode eficientemente aprender grandes quantidades de vocabulário ou de qualquer outro material. AnkiDroid lhe mostra as coisas a aprender justo antes que voce as esqueça.\n\nPara ter uma primeira impressão de como tudo funciona, nos recomendamos iniciar com um deck tutorial, o qual lhe dará alguma informação inicial, e tente um pouco. Basta clicar em \"Iniciar Revisão\' após te-lo aberto. \n\n Criar um deck tutorial agora?</string>
  <string name="check_db_title">Verificar banco de dados</string>
  <string name="check_db_result_message">Banco de dados verificado e otimizado. \nEncurtado em %d kb</string>
  <string name="contextmenu_deckpicker_delete_deck">Excluir Deck</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_title">Excluir Deck</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_message">Tem certeza que deseja excluir todas os cartões em %s?</string>
  <string name="delete_cram_deck_message">Are you sure you wish to send all cards in %s back to their original decks?</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_confirm">Exclua o</string>
  <string name="new_version_message">Novos recursos:</string>
  <string name="no_tts_available_title">Texto para fala</string>
  <string name="no_tts_available_message">Nenhum idioma disponível para reconhecimento de voz</string>
  <string name="tts_no_tts">Não fale</string>
  <string name="dont_show_again">Não mostrar novamente</string>
  <string name="sync_log_title">Log de sincronização</string>
  <string name="notify_ticker">Atualização do aplicativo</string>
  <string name="notify_title">AnkiDroid atualizado</string>
  <string name="notify_message">Baixar uma nova versão</string>
  <string name="notification_title">Confirmar atualização do AnkiDroid</string>
  <string name="notification_message">Uma nova versão do AnkiDroid está disponível no Android Market.\n\nVocê gostaria de instalá-lo?</string>
  <string name="notification_stop">Não me notificar novamente dessa atualização</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_title">Redefinir progresso do cartão</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_message">Isso redefine o progresso de aprendizagem para todos os cartões desta nota (eles vão parecer como cartões novos). \n Realmente continuar?</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_confirmation">Redefinir todos os cartões desta nota</string>
  <string name="answering_error_title">Erro de banco de dados</string>
  <string name="answering_error_message">Ocorreu um erro ao gravar à coleção. Isso poderia estar relacionado com um banco de dados corrompido ou espaço insuficiente no disco.\n\nSe isso acontece mais frequentemente, tente verificar o banco de dados, repare a coleção ou restaure-a de um backup. Clique em \'Opções\' para isso.\n\nEm todo caso, isso poderia ser um bug do AnkiDroid também; relate o erro para que possamos verificar isso.</string>
  <string name="answering_error_report">Reportar erro</string>
  <string name="repair_deck_dialog">Você realmente deseja tentar reparar o banco de dados? \n\nAntes de iniciar a tentativa, uma cópia será criado na subpasta \'%s\'.</string>
  <string name="intent_add_saved_information">Dados salvos</string>
  <string name="intent_add_clear_all">Apagar tudo</string>
  <string name="intent_aedict_empty">Categoria \'padrão\' está vazia</string>
  <string name="intent_aedict_category">Para adicionar cartões ao AnkiDroid remova todas as categorias das notas ou adicione uma com o nome \'default\'</string>
  <string name="custom_study_new_total_new">New cards in deck: %s</string>
  <string name="custom_study_rev_total_rev">Reviews due in deck: %s</string>
  <string name="custom_study_new_extend">Increase today\'s new card limit by</string>
  <string name="custom_study_rev_extend">Increase today\'s review limit by</string>
  <string name="custom_study_forgotten">Review cards forgotten in last x days:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_ahead">Review ahead by x days:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_random">Select x cards randomly from the deck:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_preview">Preview new cards added in the last x days:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_tags">Enter tags:</string>
  <string name="rebuild_custom_study_deck">Rebuilding custom study deck.\nPlease wait...</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_title">Deck Upgrade</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_rename_warning">Be aware that this will export your current collection to a file called \'%1$s\' and will create a new one from your old anki 1.x files. If desired, you can manually re-import the above apkg file after completing the wizard. Do you really want to continue?</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_already_upgraded">Version 2 of AnkiDroid uses a new format for decks.\nIf you did not successfully upgrade your decks, you can restart the upgrade now to upgrade your decks.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_major_warning"><![CDATA[This is a major update to Ankidroid and the upgrade process will take at least 10-20 minutes.<br><br>Do you want to proceed now or later?<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en">More info</a>]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_start_again_to_upgrade_toast">Please start Ankidroid again when you have time to upgrade!</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_recommended_method"><![CDATA[The recommended upgrade method is to sync with a PC and upgrade with the desktop version of Anki.<br><br>There is also an alternative method where you can upgrade over the internet if you do not have access to a PC, and your collection is not too big.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_exit">You can exit the upgrade wizard without importing your old cards by clicking the exit button below.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_new_collection">You can create a new empty collection by clicking below.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_downgrade"><![CDATA[<br><br>If you want to downgrade back to AnkiDroid 1 then please read <a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Continuing_to_use_AnkiDroid_1.1.3">these instructions</a>.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection">Create new collection</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection_title">Create New Collection</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_not_import_warning">Are you sure you want to do this? Your old data will not be imported.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_via_web"><![CDATA[<b>This upgrade method is not recommended if you used media files, or have a big collection!</b><br><br>Your Anki1 decks will be zipped and uploaded to AnkiWeb, and the converted collection will then be downloaded.<br><br>Please note that a stable internet connection is required, and that there is a 50MB file limit.<br><br>Users of Anki Desktop are strongly encouraged to use the PC based upgrade method.<br><br>Do you still want to proceed?]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_via_anki_desktop"><![CDATA[If you currently have an up-to-date version of your AnkiDroid collection in the Anki desktop software, you can upgrade from there and then download your upgraded collection by syncing with AnkiWeb.<br><br>Alternatively, you can copy your AnkiDroid collection to your PC using USB, then upgrade the collection and copy back to AnkiDroid.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_auto_upgrade"><![CDATA[Please install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection, then sync your upgraded collection with AnkiWeb and press the "Download" button.<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_2:_Using_AnkiWeb_sync">More detailed information on upgrading using AnkiWeb</a>]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_manual"><![CDATA[Please copy all of your *.anki files (and any *.media folders) from your AnkiDroid folder to your Anki Desktop folder, and then install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection.<br><br>When the upgrade is completed, please export your collection from Anki2 and copy the collection.apkg file to your AnkiDroid folder and press the Import button below.<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_1:_Using_USB_(recommended)">More detailed information on upgrading using USB.</a>]]></string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_title">Upgrade Cancelled</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_description">The upgrade attempt was cancelled, please try again one of the available upgrade methods.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_failed">The upgrade process was unsuccessful. Please try again, or choose a different upgrade method</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_exceeds">The total compressed size of your Anki1 decks exceeds the limit that the server can process (50 mb), please try upgrading with a different method.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_sdcard">The upgrade was completed, but there was an error while unpacking the resulting collection, please ensure that you have enough available disk (needed %1$d mb) and try again, or try upgrading with a different method.</string>
  <string name="export_progress_title">Collection Export</string>
  <string name="export_progress_exporting">Exporting collection, please wait…</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_export_successful">Your old collection has been successfully exported, proceeding with the upgrade process.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_export_error">Error during the export of your old collection. Would you like to continue with the upgrade process anyway (your old collection will be lost)?</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_sync_from_ankiweb">Sync from AnkiWeb</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_have_you_synced">Are you sure you have upgraded your collection with Anki Desktop 2 and synced with AnkiWeb?</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_dont_upgrade">Don\'t Upgrade</string>
  <string name="import_unpacking">Unpacking archive.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="importing_collection">Importing collection.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_media_count">Importing media files %1$d%%\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_update_counts">Updating deck counts.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_add_progress">• Unpacking archive %1$s\n• Import of notes %2$d%%\n• Import of cards %3$d%%\n• Cleanup %4$s</string>
  <string-array name="about_content">
    <item><![CDATA[<h2>%1$s:<br/>Cartões de estudo para Android</h2>AnkiDroid é a aplicação de cartões de estudo que é totalmente compatível com o software de desktop <a href="%2$s">Anki</a>. Você pode criar, baixar e aprender conteúdos em ambos,AnkiDroid ou Anki Desktop, e sincronizá-los facilmente.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Para nos ajudar a fazer o AnkiDroid melhor, por favor reporte qualquer bug <a href="%1$s">aqui</a>; novas ideias são muito bem vindas também! Por favor use o <a href="%2$s">wiki</a> e diga Oi no <a href="%3$s">fórum</a>.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[AnkiDroid é um <a href="%1$s">software open source<a/>, então todos são encorajados a <a href="%2$s">juntar-se</a> aos <a href="%3$s">colaboradores</a>:-)]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Não-desenvolvedores podem ajudar também, por exemplo <a href="%1$s">traduzindo</a> AnkiDroid, atualizando o wiki e os screenshots, <a href="%2$s">doando</a> para o Anki Desktop, ou bloggando sobre AnkiDroid!]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[AnkiDroid é publicado sobre a licensa<a href="%1$s">GNU-GPL v3 license</a> e o codigo-fonte está <a href="%2$s">aqui</a>.]]></item>
  </string-array>
</resources>
