<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thanks for installing AnkiDroid!<br />This is a short introduction.<br />What you see now is the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>question</span> part of a flashcard.<br />Please click on the large button below...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The next card is shown now.<br />The idea is straightforward: Just like in &quot;real world&quot; paper flashcards, you write a question on the front and the answer on the back side of your cards.<br />(click the button to show the back side)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Jokaisen vastauspainikkeen yläpuolella on tietoa ajasta jonka jälkeen kortti näytetään uudelleen jos sillä painikkeella vastataan.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Tarkoituksena on näyttää kortti uudelleen juuri ennen kuin unohtaisit sen. Empiiriset tutkimukset ovat osoittaneet, että tällöin tietoa opitaan tehokkaimmin.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Hieman organisoinnista AnkiDroidissa:<br /><br>Kaikki tiedot on esitettävä kysymys ja vastaus -pareina. Jos haluat oppia toiseen suuntaan, luo toinen kortti jossa tiedot on vaihdettu.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Kortit on koottu pakkoihin ja voidaan hallinnoida kaikenlaisten tunnisteiden avulla.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[There are mainly two ways of getting new cards:<br />You either add premade decks of other users (choose &quot;shared decks&quot; in the decks summary) or create them by yourself.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Joka tapauksessa, omien pakkojen luominen on välttämätöntä jos haluat räätälöidä ohjelman omiin tarpeisiisi täydellisesti sopivaksi. Voit tehdä tämän suoraan AnkiDroidista...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s have a look on the top bar:<br />In the left top corner you find some numbers. The blue one tells you, how many new cards are still projected for today. The red number counts the failed cards (answered by &quot;again&quot;),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Oikeasta yläkulmasta löydät tietoa vastausajasta tälle kortille ja suoritustasostasi.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Albeit you can use AnkiDroid stand alone, it is fully connected to AnkiWeb, the syncing server of Anki Desktop (available for Linux, Windows, Mac).]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[These have been the main points of AnkiDroid usage.<br /><br>For more information about the key concept of Anki, visit http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[... in order to see the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>answer</span> part of the flashcard (below the line).<br />Click on the button on the right]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s assume you want to learn the world\'s capitals. Let the question be...<br />(click on one of the buttons to show the next card)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Tämä aikajakso lasketaan viimeisen vastausajan, tämänhetkisen huojennusvalinnan ja kortin aikaisempien huojennusvalintojen avulla.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Jos haluat tietää lisää aikavälikertauksesta, katso:<br>http://fi.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aikavälikertaus]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Älä huoli, tämä voidaan tehdä automaattisesti. Ei ole tarpeen lisätä samoja tietoja kahdesti.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Opit sen nopeasti kun alat käyttämään AnkiDroidia.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You\'ll find thousands of premade decks to download and there are probably some which are useful for you.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[... tai (hieman mukavammin) Anki-työpöydänsovelluksella (ladattavissa ilmaiseksi osoitteesta http://ankisrs.net/).<br><br>Voit helposti synkronoida pakat työpöytäsovelluksen kanssa, joten tietojen siirto ei ole ongelma.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[the green one shows the number of cards you\'ve already learned before and which are due to review today.<br />The type of the actual cards is specified by an underline.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Ylempi palkki näyttää edistymistä, alempi tarkoittaa kyllä-vastauksia.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thus, you can easily sync your collection between AnkiDroid and Anki Desktop and use the latter for a more convenient card adding and managing.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Just try it a bit out now and see, if it fits your needs.<br><br>Maybe start with the deck overview (hit menu on the main screen and choose &quot;all decks&quot;), where you can download premade decks or create your own (just use the menu there).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>