<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Andrew <andrewdubya@gmail> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Edu Zamora <edu.zasu@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Daniel Svaerd <daniel.svard@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Nicolas Raoul <nicolas.raoul@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2010 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
<!--Generated by crowdin.net-->
<resources>
  <string name="welcome_message">With AnkiDroid, you can efficiently learn large amounts of vocabulary or any other material. AnkiDroid shows you the things to learn just before you forget them.\n\nTo get a first impression of how everything works, we recommend to start with a tutorial deck, which will give you some initial information, and try a bit out. Just just click on \"Start Reviewing\" after having opened it.\n\nCreate the tutorial deck now?</string>
  <string name="check_db_title">Έλεγχος βάσης δεδομένων</string>
  <string name="check_db_result_message">Η βάση δεδομένων ελέγχθηκε και βελτιστοποιήθηκε.\nΣυρρικνώση κατά %d kb</string>
  <string name="contextmenu_deckpicker_delete_deck">Διαγραφή Τράπουλας</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_title">Διαγραφή Τράπουλας</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_message">Είστε βέβαιοι ότι θέλετε να διαγράψετε όλες τις κάρτες στο %s?</string>
  <string name="delete_cram_deck_message">Είστε βέβαιοι ότι θέλετε να στείλετε όλες τις κάρτες της %s πίσω στο αρχικές τους τράπουλες;</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_confirm">Διαγράψτε το</string>
  <string name="new_version_message">Νέες δυνατότητες:</string>
  <string name="no_tts_available_title">Μετατροπή κειμένου σε ομιλία</string>
  <string name="no_tts_available_message">Δεν είναι διαθέσιμη η μετατροπής κειμένου σε ομιλία</string>
  <string name="tts_no_tts">Σίγαση</string>
  <string name="dont_show_again">Να μην εμφανιστεί ξανά</string>
  <string name="sync_log_title">Ημερολόγιο συχρονισμού</string>
  <string name="notify_ticker">Ανανέωση εφαρμογής</string>
  <string name="notify_title">Το AnkiDroid Ενημερώθηκε</string>
  <string name="notify_message">Κατεβάστε τη νέα έκδοση</string>
  <string name="notification_title">Επιβεβαιώστε την ενημέρωση του AnkiDroid</string>
  <string name="notification_message">Μια νέα έκδοση του AnkiDroid είναι διαθέσιμη στο Android Market.\n\nΘα θέλατε να το εγκαταστήσετε;</string>
  <string name="notification_stop">Μην με ενημερώσετε ξανά για αυτή την ανανέωση</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_title">Επαναφορά προόδου κάρτας</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_message">Αυτό επαναφέρει την πρόοδο μάθησης για όλες τις κάρτες αυτής της σημείωσης (θα μοιάζουν σαν νέες κάρτες).\nΕίστε βέβαιοι;</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_confirmation">Επαναφορά όλων των καρτών αυτής της σημείωσης</string>
  <string name="answering_error_title">Σφάλμα βάσης δεδομένων</string>
  <string name="answering_error_message">Παρουσιάστηκε σφάλμα κατά την εγγραφή στη συλλογή. Αυτό θα μπορεί να σχετίζεται με κατεστραμμένη βάση δεδομένων ή ανεπαρκή αποθηκευτικό χώρο.\n\nΑν συμβαίνει συχνά, προσπαθήστε να ελέγξετε τη βάση δεδομένων, να επιδιορθώσετε τη συλλογή ή να την επαναφέρετε από ένα αντίγραφο. Κάντε κλικ στις σχετικές «επιλογές».\n\nΕκτός αυτού, μπορεί να είναι και AnkiDroid· σφάλμα παρακαλούμε αναφέρετε το σφάλμα ώστε να το ελέγξουμε.</string>
  <string name="answering_error_report">Αναφορά σφάλματος</string>
  <string name="repair_deck_dialog">Είστε βέβαιοι ότι θέλετε να επιδιορθώσετε τη βάση δεδομένων;\n\nΠριν να ξεκινήσει η απόπειρα, θα δημιουργηθεί ένα αντίγραφο στον υποφάκελο \'%s\'.</string>
  <string name="intent_add_saved_information">Αποθηκευμένα δεδομένα</string>
  <string name="intent_add_clear_all">Καθαρισμός όλων</string>
  <string name="intent_aedict_empty">Η κατηγορία \"default\" είναι κενή</string>
  <string name="intent_aedict_category">Για να προσθέσετε κάρτες στο AnkiDroid αφαιρέστε όλες τις κατηγορίες Notepad ή προσθέστε μία με όνομα \"default\"</string>
  <string name="custom_study_new_total_new">Νέα κάρτες στην τράπουλα: %s</string>
  <string name="custom_study_rev_total_rev">Απαιτούμενες αξιολογήσεις στην τράπουλα: %s</string>
  <string name="custom_study_new_extend">Αύξηση σημερινού ορίου νέων καρτών κατά</string>
  <string name="custom_study_rev_extend">Αύξηση σημερινού ορίου επαναλήψεων κατά</string>
  <string name="custom_study_forgotten">Επανάληψη ξεχασμένων καρτών στις τελευταίες x μέρες:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_ahead">Επανάληψη μπροστά κατά x μέρες:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_random">Τυχαία επιλογή x καρτών από την τράπουλα:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_preview">Προεπισκόπηση νέων καρτών του προστέθηκαν στις τελευταίες x μέρες:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_tags">Εισάγετε ετικέτες:</string>
  <string name="rebuild_custom_study_deck">Ανασύσταση προσαρμοσμένης μελέτης.\nΠαρακαλούμε περιμένετε...</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_title">Αναβάθμιση τράπουλας</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_rename_warning">Be aware that this will export your current collection to a file called \'%1$s\' and will create a new one from your old anki 1.x files. If desired, you can manually re-import the above apkg file after completing the wizard. Do you really want to continue?</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_already_upgraded">Version 2 of AnkiDroid uses a new format for decks.\nIf you did not successfully upgrade your decks, you can restart the upgrade now to upgrade your decks.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_major_warning"><![CDATA[This is a major update to Ankidroid and the upgrade process will take at least 10-20 minutes.<br><br>Do you want to proceed now or later?<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en">More info</a>]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_start_again_to_upgrade_toast">Παρακαλούμε ξεκινήστε το Ankidroid ξανά όταν έχετε χρόνο για την αναβάθμιση!</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_recommended_method"><![CDATA[The recommended upgrade method is to sync with a PC and upgrade with the desktop version of Anki.<br><br>There is also an alternative method where you can upgrade over the internet if you do not have access to a PC, and your collection is not too big.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_exit">You can exit the upgrade wizard without importing your old cards by clicking the exit button below.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_new_collection">You can create a new empty collection by clicking below.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_downgrade"><![CDATA[<br><br>If you want to downgrade back to AnkiDroid 1 then please read <a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Continuing_to_use_AnkiDroid_1.1.3">these instructions</a>.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection">Δημιουργία νέας συλλογής</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection_title">Δημιουργία Νέας Συλλογής</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_not_import_warning">Είστε βέβαιοι ότι θέλετε να το κάνετε αυτό; Τα παλιά δεδομένα σας δεν θα εισαχθούν.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_via_web"><![CDATA[<b>This upgrade method is not recommended if you used media files, or have a big collection!</b><br><br>Your Anki1 decks will be zipped and uploaded to AnkiWeb, and the converted collection will then be downloaded.<br><br>Please note that a stable internet connection is required, and that there is a 50MB file limit.<br><br>Users of Anki Desktop are strongly encouraged to use the PC based upgrade method.<br><br>Do you still want to proceed?]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_via_anki_desktop"><![CDATA[If you currently have an up-to-date version of your AnkiDroid collection in the Anki desktop software, you can upgrade from there and then download your upgraded collection by syncing with AnkiWeb.<br><br>Alternatively, you can copy your AnkiDroid collection to your PC using USB, then upgrade the collection and copy back to AnkiDroid.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_auto_upgrade"><![CDATA[Please install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection, then sync your upgraded collection with AnkiWeb and press the "Download" button.<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_2:_Using_AnkiWeb_sync">More detailed information on upgrading using AnkiWeb</a>]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_manual"><![CDATA[Please copy all of your *.anki files (and any *.media folders) from your AnkiDroid folder to your Anki Desktop folder, and then install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection.<br><br>When the upgrade is completed, please export your collection from Anki2 and copy the collection.apkg file to your AnkiDroid folder and press the Import button below.<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_1:_Using_USB_(recommended)">More detailed information on upgrading using USB.</a>]]></string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_title">Upgrade Cancelled</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_description">The upgrade attempt was cancelled, please try again one of the available upgrade methods.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_failed">The upgrade process was unsuccessful. Please try again, or choose a different upgrade method</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_exceeds">The total compressed size of your Anki1 decks exceeds the limit that the server can process (50 mb), please try upgrading with a different method.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_sdcard">The upgrade was completed, but there was an error while unpacking the resulting collection, please ensure that you have enough available disk (needed %1$d mb) and try again, or try upgrading with a different method.</string>
  <string name="export_progress_title">Collection Export</string>
  <string name="export_progress_exporting">Exporting collection, please wait…</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_export_successful">Your old collection has been successfully exported, proceeding with the upgrade process.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_export_error">Error during the export of your old collection. Would you like to continue with the upgrade process anyway (your old collection will be lost)?</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_sync_from_ankiweb">Sync from AnkiWeb</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_have_you_synced">Are you sure you have upgraded your collection with Anki Desktop 2 and synced with AnkiWeb?</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_dont_upgrade">Don\'t Upgrade</string>
  <string name="import_unpacking">Unpacking archive.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="importing_collection">Importing collection.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_media_count">Importing media files %1$d%%\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_update_counts">Updating deck counts.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_add_progress">• Unpacking archive %1$s\n• Import of notes %2$d%%\n• Import of cards %3$d%%\n• Cleanup %4$s</string>
  <string-array name="about_content">
    <item><![CDATA[<h2>%1$s:<br/>Κάρτες για το Android</h2>Το AnkiDroid είναι μία εφαρμογή καρτών που είναι πλήρως συμβατή με το λογισμικό <a href="%2$s">Anki</a>. Μπορείτε να δημιουργήσετε, να κατεβάσετε και να μάθετε κάρτες και στα δύο, AnkiDroid ή Anki και να συγχρονίζετε μεταξύ τους πολύ εύκολα.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Για να μας βοηθήσετε να βελτιώσουμε το AnkiDroid, παρακαλούμε αναφέρετε τυχών σφάλματα <a href="%1$s">εδώ</a>. Ιδέες για νέα χαρακτηριστικά είναι ευπρόσδεκτες επίσης! Παρακαλούμε χρησιμοποιείστε το <a href="%2$s">wiki</a> και πείτε μας ένα Γεια στο <a href="%3$s">φόρουμ</a>.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Το AnkiDroid είναι <a href="%1$s">λογισμικό ανοικτού κώδικα<a/>, οπότε ο καθένας μπορεί να <a href="%2$s">συμμετάσχει</a> στους <a href="%3$s">συνησφέροντες</a>:-)]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Μη-προγραμματιστές μπορούν να βοηθήσουν επίσης, για παράδειγμα με το να <a href="%1$s">μεταφράζουν</a> το AnkiDroid, να ενημερώνουν το wiki και τις εικόνες, να <a href="%2$s">δωρίζουν</a> στο Anki Desktop, ή να κάνουν blogging για το AnkiDroid!]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Το AnkiDroid δημοσιοποιείται υπό την άδεια <a href="%1$s">GNU-GPL v3</a> και ο κώδικάς του είναι διαθέσιμος <a href="%2$s">εδώ</a>.]]></item>
  </string-array>
</resources>
