<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Andrew <andrewdubya@gmail> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Edu Zamora <edu.zasu@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Daniel Svaerd <daniel.svard@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2009 Nicolas Raoul <nicolas.raoul@gmail.com> 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2010 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
<!--Generated by crowdin.net-->
<resources>
  <string name="welcome_message">مع AnkiDroid، يمكنك أن تتعلم بكفاءة كميات كبيرة من المفردات أو أي مواد أخرى. AnkiDroid يظهر لك الأشياء التي ينبغي أن تعلم قبل أن تكون قد نسيتها.\n\nللحصول على أول انطباع عن كيفية عمل كل شيء، نوصي بأن تبدأ مع قاعدة البرنامج التعليمي، الذي سوف يعطيكم بعض المعلومات الأولية، وجرب غيرها. فقط اضغط على \"بدء استعراض\" بعد فتحها.\n\nإنشاء قاعدة تعليمية الآن؟</string>
  <string name="check_db_title">افحص قاعدة البيانات</string>
  <string name="check_db_result_message">فحصت قاعدة البيانات و حسنت.\nتقلصت بـ %d kb</string>
  <string name="contextmenu_deckpicker_delete_deck">احذف الرزمة</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_title">احذف رزمة</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_message">هل أنت متأكد من رغبتك في حذف كل البطاقات في%s؟</string>
  <string name="delete_cram_deck_message">هل أنت متأكد من رغبتك في إرسال جميع البطاقات في %s مرة أخرى إلى هذه حالتها الأصلية؟</string>
  <string name="delete_deck_confirm">إحذفه</string>
  <string name="new_version_message">الميزات الجديدة:</string>
  <string name="no_tts_available_title">نطق النصوص</string>
  <string name="no_tts_available_message">لا تتوفر  لغة لنطق النصوص</string>
  <string name="tts_no_tts">لا تنطق</string>
  <string name="dont_show_again">لا تظهر مرة أخرى</string>
  <string name="sync_log_title">سجل المزامنة</string>
  <string name="notify_ticker">تحديث البرنامج</string>
  <string name="notify_title">حدث آنكيدرويد</string>
  <string name="notify_message">حمل نسخة جديدة</string>
  <string name="notification_title">أكد تحديث أنكيدرويد</string>
  <string name="notification_message">يتوفر إصدار جديد من آنكيدرويد في سوق أندرويد. \n\n
هل ترغب في تثبيته؟</string>
  <string name="notification_stop">لا تنبهني بهذا التحديث بعد الآن</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_title">أعد تعيين مستوى تقدم التعلم</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_message">هذا سيعيد تعيين كل التقدم التعليمي لكل البطاقات لهذه الملاحظة(ستبدو وكأنها بطاقات جديدة).\nهل تريد المتابعة؟</string>
  <string name="reset_card_dialog_confirmation">أعيد تعيين كل البطاقات لهذه الملاحظة</string>
  <string name="answering_error_title">خطأ قاعدة البيانات</string>
  <string name="answering_error_message">حدث خطأ أثناء الكتابة إلى المجموعة. يمكن أن هذا ذا علاقة بقاعدة بيانات معطوبة أو المساحة القرص غير الكافية.\n\nإذا حدث هذا بشكل متكرر، الرجاء حاول فحص قاعدة البيانات،أو إصلاح المجموعة أو استعادة النسخة الاحتياطية. انقر على \'خيارات\' لفعل ذلك.\n\nومع ذلك، يمكن أن تكون علة بأنكيدرويد؛ الرجاء إرسال تقرير الخطأ حتى يمكننا تحقق منها ذلك.</string>
  <string name="answering_error_report">خطأ التقرير</string>
  <string name="repair_deck_dialog">هل تريد حقا محاولة إصلاح قاعدة البيانات؟\n\nقبل بدء هذه المحاولة، ستنشيء نسخة في مجلد فرعي \'%s\'.</string>
  <string name="intent_add_saved_information">بيانات محفوظة</string>
  <string name="intent_add_clear_all">امسح الكل</string>
  <string name="intent_aedict_empty">التصنيف \'default\' فارغ</string>
  <string name="intent_aedict_category">لإضافة بطاقات إلى آنكيدرويد أزل كل تصنيفات المفكرة أو أضف واحد باسم \'default\'</string>
  <string name="custom_study_new_total_new">بطاقات جديدة في القاعدة: %s</string>
  <string name="custom_study_rev_total_rev">Reviews due in deck: %s</string>
  <string name="custom_study_new_extend">Increase today\'s new card limit by</string>
  <string name="custom_study_rev_extend">Increase today\'s review limit by</string>
  <string name="custom_study_forgotten">Review cards forgotten in last x days:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_ahead">Review ahead by x days:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_random">Select x cards randomly from the deck:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_preview">Preview new cards added in the last x days:</string>
  <string name="custom_study_tags">Enter tags:</string>
  <string name="rebuild_custom_study_deck">Rebuilding custom study deck.\nPlease wait...</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_title">Deck Upgrade</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_rename_warning">Be aware that this will export your current collection to a file called \'%1$s\' and will create a new one from your old anki 1.x files. If desired, you can manually re-import the above apkg file after completing the wizard. Do you really want to continue?</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_already_upgraded">Version 2 of AnkiDroid uses a new format for decks.\nIf you did not successfully upgrade your decks, you can restart the upgrade now to upgrade your decks.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_major_warning"><![CDATA[This is a major update to Ankidroid and the upgrade process will take at least 10-20 minutes.<br><br>Do you want to proceed now or later?<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en">More info</a>]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_start_again_to_upgrade_toast">Please start Ankidroid again when you have time to upgrade!</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_recommended_method"><![CDATA[The recommended upgrade method is to sync with a PC and upgrade with the desktop version of Anki.<br><br>There is also an alternative method where you can upgrade over the internet if you do not have access to a PC, and your collection is not too big.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_exit">You can exit the upgrade wizard without importing your old cards by clicking the exit button below.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_new_collection">You can create a new empty collection by clicking below.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_downgrade"><![CDATA[<br><br>If you want to downgrade back to AnkiDroid 1 then please read <a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Continuing_to_use_AnkiDroid_1.1.3">these instructions</a>.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection">Create new collection</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection_title">Create New Collection</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_not_import_warning">Are you sure you want to do this? Your old data will not be imported.</string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_via_web"><![CDATA[<b>This upgrade method is not recommended if you used media files, or have a big collection!</b><br><br>Your Anki1 decks will be zipped and uploaded to AnkiWeb, and the converted collection will then be downloaded.<br><br>Please note that a stable internet connection is required, and that there is a 50MB file limit.<br><br>Users of Anki Desktop are strongly encouraged to use the PC based upgrade method.<br><br>Do you still want to proceed?]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_via_anki_desktop"><![CDATA[If you currently have an up-to-date version of your AnkiDroid collection in the Anki desktop software, you can upgrade from there and then download your upgraded collection by syncing with AnkiWeb.<br><br>Alternatively, you can copy your AnkiDroid collection to your PC using USB, then upgrade the collection and copy back to AnkiDroid.]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_auto_upgrade"><![CDATA[Please install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection, then sync your upgraded collection with AnkiWeb and press the "Download" button.<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_2:_Using_AnkiWeb_sync">More detailed information on upgrading using AnkiWeb</a>]]></string>
  <string name="deck_upgrade_manual"><![CDATA[Please copy all of your *.anki files (and any *.media folders) from your AnkiDroid folder to your Anki Desktop folder, and then install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection.<br><br>When the upgrade is completed, please export your collection from Anki2 and copy the collection.apkg file to your AnkiDroid folder and press the Import button below.<br><br><a href="http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_1:_Using_USB_(recommended)">More detailed information on upgrading using USB.</a>]]></string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_title">Upgrade Cancelled</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_description">The upgrade attempt was cancelled, please try again one of the available upgrade methods.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_failed">The upgrade process was unsuccessful. Please try again, or choose a different upgrade method</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_exceeds">The total compressed size of your Anki1 decks exceeds the limit that the server can process (50 mb), please try upgrading with a different method.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_sdcard">The upgrade was completed, but there was an error while unpacking the resulting collection, please ensure that you have enough available disk (needed %1$d mb) and try again, or try upgrading with a different method.</string>
  <string name="export_progress_title">Collection Export</string>
  <string name="export_progress_exporting">Exporting collection, please wait…</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_export_successful">Your old collection has been successfully exported, proceeding with the upgrade process.</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_export_error">Error during the export of your old collection. Would you like to continue with the upgrade process anyway (your old collection will be lost)?</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_sync_from_ankiweb">Sync from AnkiWeb</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_have_you_synced">Are you sure you have upgraded your collection with Anki Desktop 2 and synced with AnkiWeb?</string>
  <string name="upgrade_deck_dont_upgrade">Don\'t Upgrade</string>
  <string name="import_unpacking">Unpacking archive.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="importing_collection">Importing collection.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_media_count">Importing media files %1$d%%\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_update_counts">Updating deck counts.\nPlease wait…</string>
  <string name="import_add_progress">• Unpacking archive %1$s\n• Import of notes %2$d%%\n• Import of cards %3$d%%\n• Cleanup %4$s</string>
  <string-array name="about_content">
    <item><![CDATA[<h2>%1$s:<br/>البطاقات التعليمية لأندرويد</h2>آنكيدرويد تطبيق للبطاقات التعليمية متكامل بشكل كامل مع نسخة سطح المكتب <a href="%2$s">Anki</a>. يمكنك إنشاء و تحميل و تعلم المحتوى في كلاهما، آنكيدرويد و آنكي و المزامنة بينهما بكل سهولة.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[لمساعدتنا لجعل آنكيدرويد أفضل، الرجاء أبلغ عن أي علة  من  <a href="%1$s">هنا</a>، أفكار المميزات الجديدة مرحب بها أيضا! الرجاء استخدام <a href="%2$s">الويكي</a> و قل أهلا في<a href="%3$s">المنتدى</a>.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[آنكيدرويد  <a href="%1$s">برنامج مفتوح المصدر<a/>لذا كل شخص مدعوا لـ <a href="%2$s">للانضمام</a>  <a href="%3$s">للمساهمين</a>:-)]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[غير المطورين يمكنهم المساعدة أيضا، على سبيل المثال عن طريق  <a href="%1$s">ترجمة</a>ولقطات الشاشة أو  آنكيدرويد، أو تحديث الويكي  <a href="%2$s">التبرع </a> إلى برنامج أنكي لسطح المكتب أو  الكتابة عن آنكيدرويد AnkiDroid!]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[يصدر آنكيدرويد تحت  <a href="%1$s"> رخصة GNU-GPL v3 </a>  والشفرة المصدرية متوفرة <a href="%2$s">هنا</a>.]]></item>
  </string-array>
</resources>
