<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thanks for installing AnkiDroid!<br />This is a short introduction.<br /><br />What you see now is the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>question</span> part of a flashcard.<br />Please click on the large button below...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The next card is shown now.<br /><br />The idea is straightforward: Just like in &quot;real world&quot; paper flashcards, you write a question on the front and the answer on the back side of your cards.<br /><br />(click the button to show the back side)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br /><br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Above every answer buttons, you find information about the time, after which the card will be shown again when answered by this button.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The intention is to show you the card again, immediately before you would forget it. Empirical studies have shown that by this means information can be learned most efficiently.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Some words about the organisation in AnkiDroid:<br /><br>All information has to be put into pairs of question and answer. If you want to learn in the other direction, you should create another card with swapped information.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Cards are put together in decks and can there be organised by help of all sorts of tags.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[新しいカードを取得するには、主に 2 つの方法があります: <br/><br/> あらかじめ作られた他のユーザーの単語帳をダウンロードする ([すべての単語帳] のオプションメニューで [単語帳をダウンロード] を選択)か、自分で作成します。]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[しかし、とにかく、自身の単語帳をつくることは、あなたのニーズを完全に満たすためには必須です。 AnkiDroidで直接単語帳を作成できます。...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[一番上にあるバーを見てみましょう。: <br/><br/> 左上隅にいくつかの数字があります。赤い数字は (「もう一度」と答えた) 失敗したカード、]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[右隅にはあなたがこの問題で考えた時間とパフォーマンスについて表示されています。]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[These have been the main points of AnkiDroid usage.<br /><br>For more information about the key concept of Anki, visit http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[... in order to see the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>answer</span> part of the flashcard (below the line).<br /><br /><br />Click on the right one of the four buttons]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s assume you want to learn the world\'s capitals. Let the question be...<br /><br />(click on one of the buttons to show the next card)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br /><br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[This time period is calculated of the last time you answered the card, the current ease choice and ease choices of previous answers of that card.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[If you want to learn more about spaced repetition, visit:<br>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Don\'t worry, this can be done automatically. There is no need of inserting the same information twice.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You will learn about that quickly when you start to use AnkiDroid.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[ あらかじめ作られた、ダウンロードできる何千もの単語帳があり、おそらくいくつかは、あなたにとって便利なものがあるでしょう。]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[... また、もう少し便利なデスクトップ・アプリケーション Anki（http://ankisrs.net/ から無料でダウンロード可能）でも作成できます。 <br><br> デスクトップ・アプリケーションであなたの単語帳を非常に簡単に同期させることができるので、データを送るのは問題ではありません。]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[ 黒い数字は、すでに学んだカードの数を示します。これは今日復習するカードの数です。そして、青い数字は今日計画されている新しいカードがいくつあるかを表しています。 <br/><br/> 下線はカードがどの種類かを示しています。]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[上のバーはあなたの進行状況を、下のバーは正解できた回答の割合を示しています。]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Just try it a bit out now and see, if it fits your needs.<br><br>Maybe start with the deck overview (hit menu on the main screen and choose &quot;all decks&quot;), where you can download premade decks or create your own (just use the menu there).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>