<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
~ Copyright (c) 2009 Andrew <andrewdubya@gmail>
~ Copyright (c) 2009 Edu Zamora <edu.zasu@gmail.com>
~ Copyright (c) 2009 Daniel Svärd <daniel.svard@gmail.com>
~ Copyright (c) 2009 Nicolas Raoul <nicolas.raoul@gmail.com>
~ Copyright (c) 2010 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com>
~
~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under
~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software
~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later
~ version.
~
~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY
~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A
~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details.
~
~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with
~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>

<string name="welcome_message">With AnkiDroid, you can efficiently learn large amounts of vocabulary or any other material. AnkiDroid shows you the things to learn just before you forget them.\n\nTo get a first impression of how everything works, we recommend to start with a tutorial deck, which will give you some initial information, and try a bit out. Just click on \"Start Reviewing\" after having opened it.\n\nCreate the tutorial deck now?</string>
    
<string name="check_db_title">Check database</string>
<string name="check_db_result_message">Database checked and optimized.\nShrunk by %d kb</string>
    
<string name="contextmenu_deckpicker_delete_deck">Delete Deck</string>
<string name="delete_deck_title">Delete Deck</string>
<string name="delete_deck_message">Are you sure you wish to delete all cards in %s?</string>
<string name="delete_cram_deck_message">Are you sure you wish to send all cards in %s back to their original decks?</string>
<string name="delete_deck_confirm">Delete it</string>

<string name="new_version_message">AnkiDroid has been upgraded to version 2.0.2. An automatic database check will run to resolve known issues. <![CDATA[<b>This might take a few minutes.</b>]]> Changes in this release:</string>
    
<string name="no_tts_available_title">Text-to-Speech</string>
<string name="no_tts_available_message">No text-to-speech language available</string>
<string name="tts_no_tts">Don\'t speak</string>

<string-array name="about_content">
	<item><![CDATA[<h2>%1$s:<br/>Flashcards for Android</h2>AnkiDroid is a flashcard application which is fully compatible with the desktop software <a href=\"%2$s\">Anki</a>. You can create, download and learn contents on both, AnkiDroid or Anki Desktop, and synchronize them very easily.]]></item>
	<item><![CDATA[To help us make AnkiDroid better, please report any bug <a href=\"%1$s\">here</a>; new feature ideas are very welcome too! Please use the <a href=\"%2$s\">wiki</a> and say Hi on the <a href=\"%3$s\">forum</a>.]]></item>
	<item><![CDATA[AnkiDroid is <a href=\"%1$s\">open source software<a/>, so everyone is encouraged to <a href=\"%2$s\">join</a> the <a href=\"%3$s\">contributors</a>:-)]]></item>
	<item><![CDATA[Non-developers can also help, for instance by <a href=\"%1$s\">translating</a> AnkiDroid, updating the wiki and screenshots, <a href=\"%2$s\">donating</a> to Anki Desktop, or blogging about AnkiDroid!]]></item>
	<item><![CDATA[AnkiDroid is released under the <a href=\"%1$s\">GNU-GPL v3 license</a> and the source code is available <a href=\"%2$s\">here</a>.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[This package uses the <a href=\"http://www.csse.monash.edu.au/~jwb/edict.html\">EDICT</a> and <a href=\"http://www.csse.monash.edu.au/~jwb/kanjidic.html\">KANJIDIC</a> dictionary files. These files are the property of the <a href=\"http://www.edrdg.org\">Electronic Dictionary Research and Development Group</a>, and are used in conformance with the Group\'s <a href=\"http://www.edrdg.org/edrdg/licence.html\">licence</a>.]]></item>
</string-array>

<string name="dont_show_again">Don\'t show again</string>

<string name="sync_log_title">Sync Log</string>
<!-- <string name="deckpicker_upgrade_failed">Upgrading failed!</string> -->

<string name="notify_ticker">Application Update</string>
<string name="notify_title">AnkiDroid Updated</string>
<string name="notify_message">Download a new version</string>
<string name="notification_title">Confirm AnkiDroid Update</string>
<string name="notification_message">A new version of AnkiDroid is available in Android Market.\n\nWould you like to install it?</string>
<string name="notification_stop">Don\'t notify me of this update again</string>

<string name="reset_card_dialog_title">Reset card progress</string>
<string name="reset_card_dialog_message">This resets the learning progress for all cards of this note (they will look like new cards).\nReally continue?</string>
<string name="reset_card_dialog_confirmation">All cards of this note reset</string>

<string name="answering_error_title">Database error</string>
<string name="answering_error_message">An error occurred while writing to the collection. This could be related to a corrupt database or to insufficient disc space.\n\nIf it happens more often, please try to check the database, repair the collection or restoring it from a backup. Click on \'options\' for that.\n\nNevertheless, it could be an AnkiDroid bug as well; please report the error that we can check this.</string>
<string name="answering_error_report">Report error</string>

<string name="repair_deck_dialog">Do you really want to try to repair the database?\n\nBefore starting the attempt, a copy will be created in subfolder \'%s\'.</string>

<string name="intent_add_saved_information">Saved data</string>
<string name="intent_add_clear_all">Clear all</string>
<string name="intent_aedict_empty">Category \'default\' is empty</string>
<string name="intent_aedict_category">To add cards to AnkiDroid remove all Notepad categories or add one named \'default\'</string>


<string name="custom_study_new_total_new">New cards in deck: %s</string>
<string name="custom_study_rev_total_rev">Reviews due in deck: %s</string>
<string name="custom_study_new_extend">Increase today\'s new card limit by</string>
<string name="custom_study_rev_extend">Increase today\'s review limit by</string>

<string name="custom_study_forgotten">Review cards forgotten in last x days:</string>

<string name="custom_study_ahead">Review ahead by x days:</string>

<string name="custom_study_random">Select x cards randomly from the deck:</string>

<string name="custom_study_preview">Preview new cards added in the last x days:</string>

<string name="custom_study_tags">Enter tags:</string>
<string name="rebuild_custom_study_deck">Rebuilding custom study deck.\nPlease wait...</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_title">Deck Upgrade</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_rename_warning">Be aware that this will export your current collection to a file called \'%1$s\' and will create a new one from your old anki 1.x files. If desired, you can manually re-import the above apkg file after completing the wizard. Do you really want to continue?</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_major_warning"><![CDATA[This is a major update to Ankidroid and the upgrade process will take at least 10-20 minutes.<br><br>Do you want to proceed now or later?<br><br><a href=\"http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en\">More info</a>]]></string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_start_again_to_upgrade_toast">Please start Ankidroid again when you have time to upgrade!</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_recommended_method"><![CDATA[The recommended upgrade method is to sync with a PC and upgrade with the desktop version of Anki.<br><br>There is also an alternative method where you can upgrade over the internet if you do not have access to a PC, and your collection is not too big.]]></string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_exit">You can exit the upgrade wizard without importing your old cards by clicking the exit button below.</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_new_collection">You can create a new empty collection by clicking below.</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_more_options_downgrade"><![CDATA[<br><br>If you want to downgrade back to AnkiDroid 1 then please read <a href=\"http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Continuing_to_use_AnkiDroid_1.1.3\">these instructions</a>.]]></string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection">Create new collection</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_create_new_collection_title">Create New Collection</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_not_import_warning">Are you sure you want to do this? Your old data will not be imported.</string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_via_web"><![CDATA[<b>This upgrade method is not recommended if you used media files, or have a big collection!</b><br><br>Your Anki1 decks will be zipped and uploaded to AnkiWeb, and the converted collection will then be downloaded.<br><br>Please note that a stable internet connection is required, and that there is a 50MB file limit.<br><br>Users of Anki Desktop are strongly encouraged to use the PC based upgrade method.<br><br>Do you still want to proceed?]]></string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_via_anki_desktop"><![CDATA[If you currently have an up-to-date version of your AnkiDroid collection in the Anki desktop software, you can upgrade from there and then download your upgraded collection by syncing with AnkiWeb.<br><br>Alternatively, you can copy your AnkiDroid collection to your PC using USB, then upgrade the collection and copy back to AnkiDroid.]]></string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_auto_upgrade"><![CDATA[Please install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection, then sync your upgraded collection with AnkiWeb and press the \"Download\" button.<br><br><a href=\"http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_2:_Using_AnkiWeb_sync\">More detailed information on upgrading using AnkiWeb</a>]]></string>
    <string name="deck_upgrade_manual"><![CDATA[Please copy all of your *.anki files (and any *.media folders) from your AnkiDroid folder to your Anki Desktop folder, and then install and start Anki Desktop version 2.0.4 or greater to upgrade your collection.<br><br>When the upgrade is completed, please export your collection from Anki2 and copy the collection.apkg file to your AnkiDroid folder and press the Import button below.<br><br><a href=\"http://code.google.com/p/ankidroid/wiki/Upgrading?wl=en#Option_1:_Using_USB_(recommended)\">More detailed information on upgrading using USB.</a>]]></string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_title">Upgrade Cancelled</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_cancelled_description">The upgrade attempt was cancelled, please try again one of the available upgrade methods.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_failed">The upgrade process was unsuccessful. Please try again, or choose a different upgrade method</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_exceeds">The total compressed size of your Anki1 decks exceeds the limit that the server can process (50 mb), please try upgrading with a different method.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_web_upgrade_sdcard">The upgrade was completed, but there was an error while unpacking the resulting collection, please ensure that you have enough available disk (needed %1$d mb) and try again, or try upgrading with a different method.</string>
    <string name="export_progress_title">Collection Export</string>
    <string name="export_progress_exporting">Exporting collection, please wait…</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_export_successful">Your old collection has been successfully exported, proceeding with the upgrade process.</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_export_error">Error during the export of your old collection. Would you like to continue with the upgrade process anyway (your old collection will be lost)?</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_sync_from_ankiweb">Sync from AnkiWeb</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_have_you_synced">Are you sure you have upgraded your collection with Anki Desktop 2 and synced with AnkiWeb?</string>
    <string name="upgrade_deck_dont_upgrade">Don\'t Upgrade</string>
    <string name="import_unpacking">Unpacking archive.\nPlease wait…</string>
    <string name="importing_collection">Importing collection.\nPlease wait…</string>
    <string name="import_media_count">Importing media files %1$d%%\nPlease wait…</string>
    <string name="import_update_counts">Updating deck counts.\nPlease wait…</string>
    <string name="import_add_progress">• Unpacking archive %1$s\n• Import of notes %2$d%%\n• Import of cards %3$d%%\n• Cleanup %4$s</string>
</resources>
