<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thanks for installing AnkiDroid!<br />This is a short introduction.<br />What you see now is the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>question</span> part of a flashcard.<br />Please click on the large button below...]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The next card is shown now.<br />The idea is straightforward: Just like in &quot;real world&quot; paper flashcards, you write a question on the front and the answer on the back side of your cards.<br />(click the button to show the back side)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Above every answer buttons, you find information about the time, after which the card will be shown again when answered by this button.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The intention is to show you the card again, immediately before you would forget it. Empirical studies have shown that by this means information can be learned most efficiently.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Some words about the organisation in AnkiDroid:<br /><br>All information has to be put into pairs of question and answer. If you want to learn in the other direction, you should create another card with swapped information.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Cards are put together in decks and can there be organised by help of all sorts of tags.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[There are mainly two ways of getting new cards:<br />You either add premade decks of other users (choose &quot;shared decks&quot; in the decks summary) or create them by yourself.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[여하튼, 자신의 필요에 따라 카드묶음을 직접 제작하는 것이 우선이므로 직접 Ankidroid에 카드를 추가할 수도 있습니다....]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[화면 상단 상태바를 살펴보세요.:<br />왼쪽 끝에는 숫자가 씌여져 있는데 빨간색  숫자는 카드 오답 숫자를 나타냅니다.(&quot;재시도&quot;),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[화면 오른쪽 끝에는 카드를 보고 생각한 시간과 학습 수행 정보를 확인할 수 있습니다.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[AnkiDroid만을 사용할 수도 있지만 Ankidroid는 AnkiWeb과 완벽하게 동기화할 수 있으므로 데스크탑(리눅스, 윈도즈,맥)에서도 함께 활용 가능합니다.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[These have been the main points of AnkiDroid usage.<br /><br>For more information about the key concept of Anki, visit http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[... in order to see the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>answer</span> part of the flashcard (below the line).<br />Click on the button on the right]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s assume you want to learn the world\'s capitals. Let the question be...<br />(click on one of the buttons to show the next card)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[This time period is calculated of the last time you answered the card, the current ease choice and ease choices of previous answers of that card.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[If you want to learn more about spaced repetition, visit:<br>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Don\'t worry, this can be done automatically. There is no need of inserting the same information twice.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You will learn about that quickly when you start to use AnkiDroid.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You\'ll find thousands of premade decks to download and there are probably some which are useful for you.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[... 또는 (약간 더 편한 방식으로) 데스크탑 Anki 프로그램과 함께 사용하는 방법이 있습니다. (Anki는 http://ankisrs.net/에서 무료로 다운 받을 수 있습니다)..<br><br> 데스크탑 Anki 프로그램을 이용해서 Ankidroid와 아주 간단하게 동기화할 수 있습니다. 그러므로 암기 데이터를 옮기는 작업은 전혀 문제가 되지 않습니다.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[검정색 숫자는 이미 학습하였고 오늘 복습해야되는 숫자를 나타냅니다. 그리고, 파란색 숫자는 오늘 배워야할 분량의 카드 숫자를 나타냅니다. <br />실제 학습하게 되는 카드의 숫자는 밑줄이 쳐져 있습니다.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[ 위쪽 상태바에서는 진행과정을, 아래쪽 상태바에서는 정답률을 확인할 수 있습니다.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[ 그리고, AnkiDroid와  Anki 데스크탑에서 컬렉션을 동기화 시킬 수 있으므로 데스크탑 Anki를 이용해서 보다 편리하게 카드를 편집하고 관리할 수 있습니다.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Just try it a bit out now and see, if it fits your needs.<br><br>Maybe start with the deck overview (hit menu on the main screen and choose &quot;all decks&quot;), where you can download premade decks or create your own (just use the menu there).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>