<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
 <!-- 
 ~ Copyright (c) 2011 Norbert Nagold <norbert.nagold@gmail.com> 
 ~ This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it under 
 ~ the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software 
 ~ Foundation; either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later 
 ~ version. 
 ~ 
 ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY 
 ~ WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A 
 ~ PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details. 
 ~ 
 ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with 
 ~ this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>. 
 --> 
 
 
<resources> 
 <string-array name="tutorial_questions"> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thanks for installing AnkiDroid!<br />This is a short introduction.<br />What you see now is the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>question</span> part of a flashcard.<br />Please click on the large button below&#8]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[The next card is shown now.<br />The idea is straightforward: Just like in &quot;real world&quot; paper flashcards, you write a question on the front and the answer on the back side of your cards.<br />(click the button to show the back side)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;What is the capital of Burkina Faso?&quot;<br />Think a bit about the answer and click then &quot;show answer&quot;]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Powyżej każdego z przycisków odpowiedzi pokazany jest czas, po jakim karta ponownie się pojawi, jeśli odpowiesz na nią za pomocą tego przycisku.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Celem jest ponowne pokazanie karty tuż przed jej zapomnieniem.  Badania empiryczne wykazały, że w ten sposób można skuteczniej opanowywać materiał pamięciowy.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Parę słów na temat organizacji danych w AnkiDroidzie:<br /><br>Materiał do nauki musi być podzielony na pary pytań i odpowiedzi.  Do nauki w drugą stronę należy utworzyć nową kartę z odwróconą kolejnością pytania i odpowiedzi.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Karty grupowane są w taliach, w których można je organizować za pomocą przeróżnych etykiet.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[There are mainly two ways of getting new cards:<br />You either add premade decks of other users (choose &quot;shared decks&quot; in the decks summary) or create them by yourself.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[W każdym razie, tworzenie własnych talii jest nieodzowne, jeśli chcesz je mieć idealnie dopasowane do swoich potrzeb.  Można to robić bezpośrednio w AnkiDroidzie&#8]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s have a look on the top bar:<br />In the left top corner you find some numbers. The red one counts the failed cards (answered by &quot;again&quot;),]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[W prawym rogu pokazane jest, jak długo zajęło Ci zastanawianie się nad odpowiedzią i Twoje wyniki.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Albeit you can use AnkiDroid stand alone, it is fully connected to AnkiWeb, the syncing server of Anki Desktop (available for Linux, Windows, Mac).]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[To były najważniejsze zasady użytkowania AnkiDroida.<br /><br>Aby dowiedzieć się więcej na temat Anki, odwiedź http://ankisrs.net/]]></item> 
 </string-array>
 <string-array name="tutorial_answers">
    <item><![CDATA[tor>&#8230; in order to see the <span style=\'font-weight:600;\'>answer</span> part of the flashcard (below the line).<br />Click on the button on the right]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Let\'s assume you want to learn the world\'s capitals. Let the question be&#8230;<br />(click on one of the buttons to show the next card)]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[&quot;Ouagadougou&quot; is the right answer. <br />You didn\'t know it? Click &quot;again&quot; to see the card again in a couple of minutes. Otherwise, click on the other buttons, depending on the easiness of the answer.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Czas ten wyliczany jest na podstawie ostatniej daty powtórki, obecnej oceny oraz poprzednich ocen aktualnej karty.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Jeśli chcesz dowiedzieć się więcej na temat metody planowanych powtórek, zobacz: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spaced_repetition_system]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Nie martw się, można to zrobić automatycznie.  Nie ma potrzeby wprowadzania tych samych informacji dwa razy.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Szybko to zauważysz, gdy zaczniesz używać AnkiDroida.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[You\'ll find thousands of premade decks to download and there are probably some which are useful for you.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[tor>&#8230;lub (co jest trochę bardziej wygodne) za pomocą desktopowej aplikacji Anki (do pobrania za darmo z http://ankisrs.net/).<br><br>Talie można łatwo synchronizować z aplikacją desktopową, zatem przesyłanie danych nie stanowi problemu.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[the black one shows the number of cards you\'ve already learned before and which are due to review today, and the blue number tells you, how many new cards are projected for today. <br />The type of the actual cards is specified by an underline.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Górna belka pokazuje postęp, dolna procent poprawnych odpowiedzi.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Thus, you can easily sync your collection between AnkiDroid and Anki Desktop and use the latter for a more convenient card adding and managing.]]></item> 
    <item><![CDATA[Spróbuj poużywać trochę programu i przekonaj się, czy odpowiada Twoim oczekiwaniom.<br><br>Zacznij może od przeglądarki talii (z menu okna głównego wybierz &quot;Wszystkie talie&quot;), gdzie możesz pobrać gotowe talie lub tworzyć własne (użyj menu tego okna).]]></item> 
 </string-array>
</resources>